Guide to the Bella Abzug papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Subject Files
  - Subseries V.16: Energy
    - Gasoline (Box 218)
    - Geothermal Energy (Box 218)
    - Legislation--93rd Congress (Box 218)
    - Legislation--94th Congress: (Box 219)
    - Energy Conservation (HR 14696 et al.) (Box 219)
    - HR 6860 (Box 219)
    - S 622 (Oil leasing) (Box 219)
    - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA) Appropriations, Fiscal Year 1975, 1976 miscellaneous (Box 220)
    - ERDA Appropriations, FY 1976, 1977, (2 Folders) (Box 220)
    - New York City: (Box 221)
    - General (Box 221)
    - Con Edison (Box 221)
    - Con Edison--Astoria (Box 221)
    - New York State:
      - General (Box 221)
      - Legislation (Box 221)
      - Niagara-Mohawk Power Corporation (Box 221)
      - Power Authority (Box 221)
      - Reports: (Box 222)
        - New York Power Pool (5 vols.) (Box 222)
        - Con Edison- Public Service (Box 222)
        - Commission Case 26827, (2 volumes) (Box 222)
        - New York State Reports: (Box 223)
        - Con Edison--Public Service (Box 223)
        - Commission Case 26827, (4 volumes) (Box 223)
        - Arthur D. Little, Inc., Report on Con Edison to the Public Service Commission, 1975-1979, (11 volumes) (Box 224)
    - Nixon, Richard M.--Administration Programs and Positions (Box 225)
    - Oil--Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 225)
    - Oil: (Box 226)
      - General (Box 226)
      - Allocation (Box 226)
      - Business and Industry (Box 226)
      - Divestiture (Box 226)
    - Oil: (Box 227)
      - Imports and exports (Box 227)
      - Indochina Middle East and Arab Embargo Offshore Oil Prices (Box 227)
      - Price Decontrol Storage (Box 227)
      - Tankers and Spills (Box 227)
      - Waste (Box 227)
    - Oil--Printed--Congressional Records, Miscellaneous (Box 228)
    - Oil Shale (Box 228)
    - Project Independence (Box 228)
    - Solar Energy (Box 228)
    - Sources of Energy, Miscellaneous (Box 228)
    - Student Exposition on Energy Resources (SEER) (Box 229)
    - Synthetic Fuels, (2 Folders) (Box 229)
    - Taxes (Box 229)
    - Transportation Aspects (Box 229)
    - Wood (Box 229)
    - Printed: (Box 230)
      - Reports--Business and Industry (Box 230)
      - Reports and Periodicals, Miscellaneous (Box 230)
      - Clippings (Gas and Oil) (Box 230)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 230)
  - Subseries V.17: Energy, Nuclear
    - Correspondence (Box 231)
    - Abzug:
      - Legislation and Amendments (Box 231)
      - Notes, memoranda, miscellaneous (Box 231)
      - Press releases and form letters (Box 231)
      - Speeches, statements, articles, Congressional Record reprints (Box 231)
    - General, 1971-1976 (Box 232)
    - Atomic Energy Commission:
      - General (Box 232)
      - Legislation (Box 232)
    - Business and Industry (Box 233)
    - Congress, U.S.: (Box 233)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy (Box 233)
    - Select Committee on Nuclear Proliferation (Box 233)
    - Gravel, Mike (U.S. Senator) (Box 233)
    - International Agreements (Israel, Egypt, India, etc.) (Box 233)
    - Legislation: (Box 234)
      - General 93rd Congress:
        - HR 1189 (Box 234)
        - HR 13565 (Box 234)
        - HR 15323 (Box 234)
        - HR 15416 (Box 234)
        - HR 15582 (s 3698) (Box 234)
      - 94th Congress:
        - HR 3474 (Box 234)
        - HR 86 31 (Box 234)
        - HR 10451 (Box 234)
        - HR 13350 (Box 234)
        - S 1439 (Box 234)
    - New York State (Box 235)
    - Nuclear-Free Zones (Box 235)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission:
      - General (Box 235)
      - Legislation (Box 235)
      - Pollard, Robert (Box 235)
      - Reports, 1974-1976, (4 Folders) (Box 236)
    - Organizations (Box 237)
    - Plutonium (Box 237)
    - Power plants--General (Box 237)
    - Power Plants--New York state--General (Box 237)
    - Power Plants--New York State: (Box 237)
    - Indian Point--Correspondence, Abzug notes, statements, General (Box 237)
    - Power Plants--New York State: (Box 238)
    - Indian Point--Agreement Hearings Testimony (Box 238)
    - Power Plants--Rasmussen Report (safety) (Box 238)
    - Proliferation (Box 238)
    - Radiation (Box 238)
    - Safety and sabotage (Box 238)
    - Scientists' Institute for Public Awareness (Box 239)
    - Transportation of Hazardous Materials: (Box 239)
    - General (Box 239)
    - Abzug statement, notes, & memos (Box 239)
    - Hearings, Testimony, legislation- (Box 239)
    - Triga Reactor, Columbia University, (2 Folders) (Box 240)
    - Weapons:
      - General (Box 240)
      - Legislation (Box 240)
      - Strategic Arms Limitation (SALT) Talks (Box 240)
      - Test Bans and Disarmament--General (Box 241)
      - Test Ban--Amchitka (Cannikin Project) (Box 241)
      - Test Ban, Comprehensive (Box 241)
    - Printed, (2 Folders) (Box 241)
  - Subseries V.18: Environment
    - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 242)
    - Abzug--Statements, Articles, Legislation, Notes, Memos (Box 242)
    - General (1) (Box 242)
    - General (2) (Box 244)
    - Air Pollution: (Box 244)
    - Correspondence (Box 244)
    - General (Box 244)
    - Air Pollution: (Box 245)
    - Auto Emission Control (Box 245)
    - Clean Air Act and amendments (Box 245)
    - New York City (Box 245)
    - New York City and State (Box 245)
    - Business and Industry (Box 245)
    - Congress, U.S.--Conservation and Natural Resources Subcommittee (Box 246)
    - Environmental Action Coalition (Box 246)
    - Fluorocarbons (Box 246)
    - Jobs and the Environment (Box 246)
    - Land Use: (Box 247)
      - Correspondence (Box 247)
      - General (Box 247)
      - Alaska Land Claims (Box 247)
      - Legislation (Box 247)
      - Parks and Recreation (Box 247)
    - Legislation: (Box 248)
    - General (Box 248)
    - National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA) (Box 248)
    - New York City:
      - General (Box 248)
      - Bridge tolls (Box 248)
      - North River Sewage Treatment Plant Sanitation (Box 248)
    - New York State: (Box 249)
      - General (Box 249)
      - Publications (2 fo1ders) (Box 249)
    - Noise Pollution:
      - General (Box 249)
      - New York City (Box 249)
      - New York City--Riverda1e Air Traffic (Box 249)
    - Population (Box 250)
    - Recycling (Box 250)
    - Sanitation and Solid Waste Disposal (Box 250)
    - Strip Mining (Box 250)
    - Timber and Forests (Box 251)
    - U.S. Environmental Agency (EPA)—correspondence (Box 251)
    - U.S.E.P.A.--General (Box 251)
    - Water Pollution--correspondence (Box 251)
    - Water Pollution: (Box 252)
      - Abzug--Notes, memos, statements, etc. (Box 252)
      - General (Box 252)
      - Legislation:
        - General (Box 252)
        - Sect. 404, W.P.Contro1 Act (Box 252)
        - PL 92-500 (Box 252)
        - HR 9650 (Box 253)
        - HR 10366 (Box 253)
        - HR 11896 (s 2770), (2 Folders) (Box 253)
      - Printed (Box 254)
    - New York State Sludge (Box 254)
    - Waste Water Treatment Printed (Box 254)
    - Water Resources: (Box 255)
      - General (Box 255)
      - Abzug--Notes (Box 255)
      - Dams and Locks: (Box 255)
      - Dickey-Lincoln (Box 255)
      - No. 26 (Alton, Ill.) (Box 255)
      - Tocks Island (Box 255)
      - Hudson River (Box 255)
      - Legislation and Projects (1) (Box 255)
    - Water Resources: (Box 256)
      - Legislation and Projects (2) (Box 256)
      - New York State (Box 256)
      - Oceans and Coastal Policy (Box 256)
    - Weather Modification (Box 256)
    - Printed Material: (Box 257)
    - Environmental Quality, annual reports of the Council on Environmental Quality. Three volumes, loose: 1972, 1973 1975. (Box 257)
    - Clippings and miscellaneous (Box 257)
  - Subseries V.19: Federal Agencies
    - General: (Box 258)
    - Correspondence (Box 258)
    - Forms and Related Material (Box 258)
    - Action: (Box 258)
    - General (Box 258)
    - VISTA (Box 258)
    - Agriculture, Department of (Box 258)
    - Census Bureau (Box 258)
    - Central Intelligence Agency: (Box 258)
    - General (Box 258)
    - Printed (Box 258)
    - Civil Service: (Box 259)
    - Correspondence (Box 259)
    - Printed (Box 259)
    - Commerce, Department of:
      - General (Box 259)
      - Consumer Affairs (Box 259)
    - Comptroller General of the United States (Box 259)
    - Defense, Department of (Box 259)
    - District of Columbia (Box 259)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 259)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (Box 259)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 259)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 259)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 259)
    - Federal Reserve Board, (2 Folders) (Box 260)
    - Food and Drug Administration: (Box 260)
    - General, (2 Folders) (Box 260)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA): (Box 261)
      - Contraceptives (Box 261)
      - Diethylstilbestrol (DES) (Box 261)
      - Estrogen (Box 261)
      - Fluoridation (Box 261)
      - Health and Food Supplements Regulations (Box 261)
      - Labeling (Box 261)
      - Regulations, Misc. (Box 261)
      - Vitamins (Box 261)
    - General Accounting Office (Box 262)
    - General Services Administration (Box 262)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of, (2 Folders) (Box 262)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 262)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 262)
    - Intelligence Agencies, General (Box 262)
    - Interior, Department of (Box 262)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 262)
    - Justice Department (Box 263)
    - Labor, Department of (Box 263)
    - Library of Congress (Box 263)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) (Box 263)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Correspondence, (2 Folders) (Box 263)
    - OEO: (Box 264)
      - General Health Centers (Box 264)
      - Legal Services, (2 Folders) (Box 264)
      - Loan Program (Box 265)
      - Publications (Box 265)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 265)
    - Overseas Private Investment Corporation (Box 265)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box 265)
    - State, Department of (Box 265)
    - U. S. Information Agency (Box 265)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 265)
    - SEE ALSO: Related subject headings (Box 265)
  - Subseries V.20: Food and Nutrition
    - Agriculture--Correspondence (Box 266)
    - Agriculture--General New York state (Box 266)
    - Congress, U.S.--House Concurrent Resolution 393 (Box 266)
    - Food--General (Box 266)
    - Food Additives (Box 266)
    - Food Prices (Box 266)
    - Food stamps: (Box 267)
      - Correspondence (Box 267)
      - Abzug--Notes and Memoranda (Box 267)
      - Statements, Legislation, Activities (Box 267)
      - General (Box 267)
      - Agriculture, U. S. Department of (Box 267)
      - Congress, U.S.--House Committee on Agriculture (Box 268)
      - Handbooks and pamphlet (Box 268)
      - Hearings and testimony (Box 268)
      - Legislation:
        - General (Box 268)
        - HR 7887 (Box 268)
        - S.S.I. (Box 268)
      - New York City New York state, (2 Folders) (Box 269)
      - Organizations:
        - General (Box 269)
        - Community Action for Legal Services (CALS) (Box 269)
        - CALS--Breadlines (Box 269)
        - Community Nutrition Institute (Box 270)
        - National Food Stamp Information Committee (Box 270)
      - Puerto Rico (Box 270)
      - Reports, miscellaneous (Box 270)
      - Printed (Box 270)
    - Legislation:
      - Food for Peace (Box 270)
      - Rice Production Act, 1975 (Box 270)
    - Nutrition--General (Box 270)
    - Programs, Miscellaneous (Box 271)
    - School Lunch Programs, (2 Folders) (Box 271)
    - Summer Lunch Programs (Box 271)
    - U.S.S.R.--Grain Deals (Box 271)
  - Subseries V.21: Ford, Gerald R.
    - Correspondence about (Box 272)
    - General (Box 272)
    - Nixon, Richard M.--Pardon:
      - Correspondence (Box 272)
      - General (Box 272)
      - Legal literature and related material
        - Resolution of Inquiry: (Box 273)
          - General (Box 273)
          - Abzug Notes & Memos Statements, Legislation, etc. (Box 273)
          - Legal literature and miscellaneous printed (Box 273)
    - State of the Union Message, 1976
      - Vice-Presidential Nomination: (Box 273)
      - Correspondence (Box 273)
      - General (Box 273)
      - Abzug Notes, statements etc. (Box 273)
      - Americans for Democratic Action (Box 273)
    - White House Press Releases (Box 273)
  - Subseries V.22: Foreign Affairs
    - Correspondence, (2 Folders) (Box 274)
    - Abzug: (Box 274)
    - Notes, memoranda, statements, legislation (Box 274)
    - Executive Protective Service Bill (Box 274)
    - General (Box 274)
    - Central Intelligence Agency--Foreign Operations (Box 274)
    - Foreign Aid: (Box 275)
      - Correspondence (Box 275)
      - Abzug--Statements (Box 275)
      - General (Box 275)
      - Agency for International Development (AID) (Box 275)
      - Military Assistance (Box 275)
      - Printed (Box 275)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 276)
      - 1973
        - General (Box 276)
        - Foreign Assistance Act (Box 276)
      - 1974 (Box 276)
      - 1975 (Box 276)
      - General (Box 276)
      - Foreign Assistance Act (Box 276)
      - 1976 (Box 277)
        - General (Box 277)
        - International Security Assistance, (2 Folders) (Box 277)
      - 1977
        - General (Box 277)
        - International Security Assistance (Box 277)
    - Legislation--International Organizations and Movements, 1973 (Box 278)
    - Multi-National Corporations (Box 278)
    - Narcotics Control--Asia (Box 278)
    - Prisons, Americans in Foreign (Box 278)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 278)
    - Sea Law (Box 278)
    - Trade: (Box 279)
      - Abzug--Notes, memos, statements, legislation (Box 279)
      - General (Box 279)
      - Legislation:
        - General (Box 279)
        - Export Administration Act (Box 279)
      - Tariffs (Box 279)
    - Printed (Box 279)
    - United Nations--Correspondence (Box 279)
    - United Nations: (Box 280)
      - General (Box 280)
      - Bunche, Ralph J. S (Box 280)
      - Israel--Expulsion (Box 280)
      - Zionism Resolution (Box 280)
      - Printed (Box 280)
      - World Peace Tax Fund (Box 280)
      - Printed (Box 280)
    - Africa (Box 281)
    - Angola: (Box 281)
    - General (Box 281)
    - Printed (Box 281)
    - Argentina (Box 281)
    - Armenia (Box 281)
    - Bangladesh and Pakistan (Box 281)
    - Brazil (Box 281)
    - Canada (Box 281)
    - Chile:
      - Correspondence (Box 281)
      - Abzug--Notes, memos and statements (Box 281)
      - General (Box 281)
      - Allende, Hortensia, Beatriz and Isabel (Box 282)
      - Hearings (Box 282)
      - Letelier, Orlando S (Box 282)
      - Organization of American States (Box 282)
      - Torture Ship (Esmeralda) (Box 282)
      - Printed (Box 282)
    - China (Box 283)
    - Cuba (Box 283)
    - Culebra (Box 283)
    - Diego Garcia (Box 283)
    - Dominican Republic (Box 283)
    - Federal Republic of Germany (West Germany) (Box 283)
    - German Democratic Republic (East Germany) (Box 283)
    - Guam (Box 283)
    - Guinea Haiti (Box 283)
    - Iceland (Box 284)
    - India (Box 284)
    - Iran (Box 284)
    - Ireland:
      - Correspondence (Box 284)
      - Abzug--Statements, notes and memoranda (Box 284)
      - General (Box 284)
      - Printed (Box 284)
    - Italy (Box 284)
    - Japan (Box 284)
    - Korea (Box 284)
    - Latin America (Box 284)
    - Mexico (Box 285)
    - Philippines (Box 285)
    - Portugal (Box 285)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 285)
    - Rhodesia (Box 286)
    - Romania (Box 286)
    - South Africa (Box 286)
    - Spain:
      - General (Box 286)
      - Abzug--statements, notes and memoranda (Box 286)
    - Thailand (Box 286)
    - Uganda (Box 286)
    - Ukraine (Box 286)
    - U.S.S.R. (Box 286)
    - Uruguay (Box 286)
    - Greece/Turkey/Cyprus--Correspondence, (4 Folders) (Box 287)
    - Greece/Turkey/Cyprus: (Box 288)
      - Abzug--Statements, notes, memos (Box 288)
      - General (Box 288)
      - Greek News Agency, London (Box 288)
      - Reports and propaganda pamphlets (Box 288)
      - Turkey--Correspondence (Box 289)
      - Turkey, Aid to--Correspondence, (2 Folders) (Box 289)
      - Turkey, Aid to--General (Box 289)
      - Turkey--Embassy (Box 290)
      - Turkey—Opium (Box 290)
      - Printed--Periodicals (Box 290)
      - Printed--Miscellaneous (Box 290)
    - Middle East: (Box 291)
      - Correspondence (Box 291)
      - Abzug--Statements, notes and memoranda (Box 291)
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 291)
      - American Friends Service Committee (Box 292)
      - Egypt (Box 292)
      - Israel:
        - Correspondence (Box 292)
        - Abzug: (Box 292)
        - Statements, notes, etc. (Box 292)
        - Trip, 1971 (Box 292)
        - Trip, 1973 (Box 292)
        - General (Box 293)
        - Aid to—Correspondence (Box 293)
        - General (Box 293)
        - Brown, General George S. (Box 293)
        - Congress, U.S.--Votes on Israel (Box 293)
        - Prisoners of War (Box 294)
        - Rabin, Yitzhak (Box 294)
        - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 294)
        - Photographs (Box 294)
      - Jordan (Box 294)
      - Lebanon (Box 294)
      - Palestinians and Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO) (Box 295)
      - Sinai Agreements, 1975, (2 Folders) (Box 295)
      - Printed--Near East Report--Miscellaneous (Box 295)
  - Subseries V.23: Grants
    - General, 1971-1975 (Box 296)
    - Notifications received, congratulation sent, 1975 (Box 296)
    - Notifications received, congratulation not sent, 1975 (Box 297)
    - 1976, (2 Folders) (Box 297)
    - Addiction Research and Treatment Corporation (Box 298)
    - Advocates for Women (Box 298)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine (Box 298)
    - Alianza (Box 298)
    - Amas Repertory Theatre (Box 298)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Administration (Box 298)
    - American Council for Émigrés in Professions (Box 298)
    - American Geographical Society (Box 298)
    - Ardis Commune (Box 298)
    - Association of New York Neighborhood Health Centers, Inc (Box 298)
    - Association for Puerto Rican Hispanic Culture (Box 298)
    - Bank Street College of Education Bilingual Education, (3 Folders) (Box 298)
    - Board of Education Bilingual Resource Center (Box 298)
    - Board of Education--Community School District 6 (Box 298)
    - Board of Education--Community School District 19 Board of Jewish Education, Inc. (Box 298)
    - Broadside--Bicentennial Program (Box 298)
    - Bronx Community College Orchestra (Box 298)
    - Bronx Community College Hall of Fame Bronx County Historical Society Bureau of Rodent Control (Box 298)
    - Cabrini Health Care Center--Dental care for handicapped (Box 299)
    - Caring Community (St. Vincent’s) (Box 299)
    - Center for Policy Research e (Box 299)
    - Cerebral Palsied Children's Summer Camp (Box 299)
    - Chelsea Coordinating Committee on Drug Addiction (Box 299)
    - Child Abuse Prevention and Treatment Act, (2 Folders) (Box 299)
    - Children's Arts and Sciences Workshops Chinatown Post Office (Box 299)
    - City College of NY--Workshop Center for Open Education City University of New York (Box 299)
    - Clinton Area Pre-School Head Start (Box 299)
    - Coastal Zone Management Act, 1972 (Box 300)
    - Collaborative University-Union Program in Applied (Box 300)
    - Social Science (Box 300)
    - Columbia University:
      - Casa Italiana (Box 300)
      - College of Physicians and Surgeons (Box 300)
      - Community Mental Health (Box 300)
      - Right to Read--Project Double Discovery (Box 300)
      - School of Nursing (Box 300)
      - Special Education Department (Box 300)
    - Community Environment Inc., (2 Folders) (Box 300)
    - Community Film Workshop Council (Box 300)
    - Community School District 2--Project Omnibus Outreach (Box 300)
    - Consumer Advocate Program, NYC (Box 300)
    - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines (Box 300)
    - Direct Theatre (Box 300)
    - District 12 Community Education Center (Box 300)
    - Dog Studies (Box 300)
    - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (Box 300)
    - French and Polyclinic Hospital Gemini Films, Inc. (Box 300)
    - Hale House (Child Abuse) (Box 300)
    - Handicapped Adults Association (Box 300)
    - Health Maintenance Organizations (Box 300)
    - Hellenic American Neighborhood Action Committee (Box 301)
    - Henry Street Settlement (Box 301)
    - Homebound Outreach Program for the Elderly (Box 301)
    - Housing--Morgan Annex (Box 301)
    - Housing Conservation Coordinators Hudson Guild (Box 301)
    - Hudson Guild--Project Share (Box 301)
    - Hunter College--Cross Cultural, Cross Regional Project (Box 301)
    - In Touch Networks (Box 301)
    - Institute for Public Transportation Irish Arts Center (Box 301)
    - Isabella Geriatric Center (Box 301)
    - Jewish Memorial Hospital Department of Hematology (Box 301)
    - Job Corps--YWCA Extension Residence Program (Box 301)
    - John Jay College of Criminal Justice (Box 301)
    - Joint Schools Committee for Academic Excellence Now, Inc. (Box 301)
    - Joint Schools Committee for Academic Excellence Now, Inc. (Box 302)
    - Kidney Dialysis (Box 302)
    - Knickerbocker Hospital (Box 302)
    - Krumb, Henry, School of Mines (Box 302)
    - Lady Carpenter (Box 302)
    - Lamda Legal Defense (Box 302)
    - Language Lab (Box 302)
    - Lehman, Orin--National Parks Service (Box 302)
    - Lehman College School of Nursing (Box 302)
    - Logan, Arthur C., Memorial Hospital (Box 302)
    - Lower East Side Economic Development Association for Cooperatives (Box 302)
    - Machinists and Aerospace Union Training Program (Box 303)
    - Machon Chana Women's Institute (Box 303)
    - Marcuse, Peter--Columbia University School of Urban Planning (Box 303)
    - Mary McLeod Bethune Senior Center (Box 303)
    - Mid-West Community Corporation (Box 303)
    - Mini-Cancer Detection Facility, United Cancer Institute (Box 303)
    - Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center (Box 303)
    - National Coordinating Council on Drug Education (Box 303)
    - National Council of Negro Women (Box 303)
    - National Project Center for Film and the Humanities (Box 303)
    - National Puerto Rican Forum (Box 303)
    - New Dimensions in Comprehensive Health, Inc. (Box 303)
    - New Future Foundation--Reading Skills Proposal (Box 303)
    - New York Association for Brain Injured Children (Box 303)
    - New York Association for Retarded Children (Box 303)
    - New York City Agency for Child Development--Head Start Program (Box 303)
    - New York City Board of Education--Ethnic Heritage Studies (Box 303)
    - New York City Parks Department (Box 303)
    - New York City Schools--Title I funding New York City Urban Corps (Box 303)
    - New York City Urban Corps--MASH Program (Box 303)
    - New York Community Trust (Box 304)
    - New York Regional Medical Program (Box 304)
    - New York University Medical Center--Sudden Infant Death (Box 304)
    - New York University Primate Center (Box 304)
    - North American Jewish Student Appeal (Box 304)
    - Nuevos Horizontes USA (Box 304)
    - Nutrition and Health Programs for Senior Citizens (Box 304)
    - Off-Theatre--New York Society for Ethical Culture (Box 304)
    - Phoenix-Hart Island (Box 304)
    - Piper's Hill, Inc. (Box 304)
    - Pisacano, Andrea (Box 304)
    - Police Athletic League (Box 304)
    - Polling Magazine--United Cerebral Palsy of NYC (Box 304)
    - Program for the Study of Crime and Delinquency (Box 305)
    - project Find (Box 305)
    - Project Seed (Box 305)
    - Puerto Rican Dance Theatre, Inc. (Box 305)
    - Puerto Rican Food Stamps (Box 305)
    - Puerto Rican Interagency Council (Box 305)